Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Scripts
  - The Shadow, Brazilian broadcast
    - 1941-42 season, 5 folders (Box 400)
      no. 2 A Estalagem da Morte (Assignment of Murder) (also labeled no. 12), 27 pp.
      no. 3 A Joia Fatidica (Dragon's Tongue Murders) (also labeled no. 32), 21 pp.
      no. 4 A Navio Negreiro (The Hoodoo Ship) (also labeled no. 36), 24 pp.
      no. 5 A Hora do Diabo (The Devil's Hour) (also labeled no. 167), 24 pp.
      no. 6 A Vingana do Gangster (Terror by Night) (also labeled no. 48), 23 pp.
      no. 7 A Morte na Universidade (The Organ Played at Midnight) (also labeled no. 30), 26 pp.
      no. 8 A Pista Enganadora (The Case of the Three Frightened Policemen) (also labeled no. 76), 20 pp.
      no. 9 O Anel Luminoso (The Circle of Light) (also labeled no. 33), 27 pp.
      no. 10 Os Mendigos da Morte (Beggars of Death) (also labeled no. 34), 25 pp.
      no. 11 A Serpente Vingadora (The Case of Baldring Heights) (also labeled no. 40), 23 pp.
      no. 12 O Vampiro (The Undead) (also labeled no. 86), 22 pp.
      no. 13 A Vingana do Sentenciado (Death Imported) (also labeled no. 94), 23 pp.
      no. 16 O Juiz Alma Negra (Drums of Death) (also labeled no. 84), 19 pp.
      no. 17 O Monstro do Pantano (The Thing in the Swamp) (also labeled no. 87), 17 pp.
      no. 18 A Ultima Representao (Dead Man's Revenge) (also labeled no. 82), 19 pp.
      no. 19 A Volta de Anatole Chevanic (The Return of Anatole Chevanic) (also labeled no. 85), 19 pp.
      no. 20 Um Crime Quasi Perfeito (Design for Death) (also labeled no. 79), 22 pp.
      no. 21 A Morte Sempre Condena (Death Speaks Twice) (also labeled no. 83), 21 pp.
      no. 22 A Morte Concede Bis (Death Gives an Encore) (also labeled no. 78), 20 pp.
      no. 23 O Raio da Morte (Dead Men Tell) (also labeled no. 92), 25 pp.
      no. 24 Um Caso de Traio (Death for a Messenger) (also labeled no. 88), 20 pp.
      no. 25 O Altar da Morte (Altar of Death) (also labeled no. 97), 22 pp.
      no. 26 Ambio Assassina (Murder Deferred) (also labeled no. 80), 19 pp.
    - 1942-43 season, 4 folders (Box 400)
      no. 2 A Maldio do Magico (Death Comes to a Magician) (also labeled no. 24), 27 pp.
      no. 7 Enterrado em Vida (The Wailing Corpse) (also labeled no. 31), 23 pp.
      no. 8 O Sombra' Enganado (Star of the Oriente) (also labeled no. 72), 23 pp.
      no. 9 A Dama de Negro (The Lady in Black) (also labeled no. 35), 24 pp.
      no. 10 O Castigo Vem do Alto (Death from the Sky) (also labeled no. 198), 23 pp.
      no. 11 A Flexa da Morte (Death Shoots an Arrow) (also labeled no. 67), 27 pp.
      no. 12 O Carrilho da Morte (The Bells Toll Death) (also labeled no. 45), 22 pp.
      no. 13 A Caveira Que Fala (The Case of the Talking Skull) (also labeled no. 66), 23 pp.
      no. 15 A Experiencia no Condenado (The Glowing Death) (also labeled no. 64), 20 pp.
      no. 19 Arma Secret (The Secret Weapon) (also labeled no. 37), 23 pp.
      no. 20 A Cano do Pavor (The Song of Fear) (also labeled no. 61), 25 pp.
      no. 21 A Marca de Cain (The Mark of Cain) (also labeled no. 46), 21 pp.
      no. 22 A Linguagem dos Mortos (The Language of the Dead) (also labeled no. 47), 22 pp.
      no. 23 A Toque da Morte (The Touch of Death) (also labeled no. 42), 20 pp.
      no. 24 A Vida Comprada (The Man Who Bought Life) (also labeled no. 74), 26 pp.
      no. 26 A Volta do Morto (The Mistery [sic] of Snake House) (also labeled no. 50), 21 pp.
    - 1943-44 season, 4 folders (Box 401)
      no. 1 O Bosque Mal Assombrado (The Gibbering Things) (also labeled no. 53), 23 pp.
      no. 2 A Bola de Cristal (The Crystal Globe) (also labeled no. 38), 26 pp.
      no. 3 Miniaturas da Morte (Dolls of Death) (also labeled no. 55), 22 pp.
      no. 4 O Mistrio do Mausolo (The Weird Sisters) (also labeled no. 65), 25 pp.
      no. 5 O Homem que No Podia Morrer (The Man Who Could not Die) (also labeled no. 59), 24 pp.
      no. 6 O Sanatrio da Morte (The Secret of the Valhalla Lodge) (also labeled no. 62), 24 pp.
      no. 7 O Navio Condenado (Ship of Doom) (also labeled no. 71), 23 pp.
      no. 8 O Fantasma do Arranha-Cu (The Phantom of the Skyscraper) (also labeled no. 57), 26 pp.
      no. 9 `O Sombra' Descoberto (The Secret of the Shadow) (also labeled no. 54), 22 pp.
      no. 10 A Morte no Cemitrio (Death at Graveyard Post) (also labeled no. 70), 29 pp.
      no. 11 A Casa Maldita (Bubbling Death) (also labeled no. 68), 25 pp.
      no. 12 A Corrida com a Morte (The Race with Death) (also labeled no. 69), 25 pp.
      no. 13 O Clube dos Condenados (Club of Doom) (also labeled no. 43), 25 pp.
      no. 14 O Invento Secreto (The Juggernaut) (also labeled no. 51), 22 pp.
      no. 15 A Serpente Negra (The Black Serpent) (also labeled no. 44), 24 pp.
      no. 16 A Beleza Sinistra (The Case of the Immortal Beauty) (also labeled no. 58), 24 pp.
      no. 17 A Morte Ataca de Madrugada (Death Stalks at Night) (also labeled no. 81), 20 pp.
      no. 18 O Domino Vermelho (The Red Domino) (also labeled no. 39), 28 pp.
      no. 19 O Morto que Pensa (The Case of the Avenging Brain) (also labeled no. 49), 22 pp.
      no. 21 As Chamas da Morte (Flames of Death) (also labeled no. 63), 23 pp.
      no. 22 A Mo que Sentia Fome (The Hungry Hand) (also labeled no. 60), 22 pp.
      no. 23 O Chamado da Morte (The Death Ride) (also labeled no. 52), 25 pp.
      no. 24 A Vingana da Morta (The House Where Madness Dwelt) (also labeled no. 77), 22 pp.
      no. 25 O Sombra em Perigo (Death to the Shadow) (also labeled no. 41), 24 pp.
      no. 26 O Mistrio do Bracelete (Drums of Doom) (also labeled no. 107), 26 pp.
      no. 27 O Sono da Imortalidade (Death in the Tomb) (also labeled no. 105), 26 pp.
      no. 28 A Morte Escreve a Historia (Death Makes the Headline) (also labeled no. 110), 26 pp.
      no. 29 Encontro com a Morte (A Date with Death) (also labeled no. 91), 20 pp.
    - 1944-45 season, 2 folders (Box 401)
      no. 1 A Deusa do Congo (The Ebony Goddess) (also labeled no. 96), 24 pp.
      no. 2 O Bilhete do Sweepstake (The Sweepstake Ticket) (also labeled no. 100), 24 pp.
      no. 3 A Morte Paga o Premio (Death Pays the Premium) (also labeled no. 95), 22 pp.
      no. 4 A Morte Ronda no Mar (The Rocks of Doom) (also labeled no. 89), 21 pp.
      no. 5 Ladroes de Taxis (The Stolen Cab Racket) (also labeled no. 106), 25 pp.
      no. 6 O Misterio de Zorgo e Joko (Halloween in Vermont) (also labeled no. 204), 27 pp.
      no. 7 Assassinato no Museu (Murder in the Museum) (also labeled no. 98), 24 pp.
      no. 8 A Morte Pesca no Mar (Death Goes Fishing) (also labeled no. 111), 26 pp.
      no. 9 Pesadelos que Matam (The Man Who Dreamed too Much) (also labeled no. 93), 26 pp.
      no. 10 O Estranho Poder (The Man who Wished Death) (also labeled no. 90), 21 pp.
    - 1944-45 season (cont.), 4 folders (Box 402)
      no. 11 O Lagarto do Fogo (The Lizard of Fire) (also labeled no. 99), 20 pp.
      no. 12 O Enigma de Caim (The Immortal Murderer) (also labeled no. 109), 23 pp.
      no. 13 O Cavaleiro Fantasma (The Ghost on Horseback) (also labeled no. 75), 24 pp.
      no. 15 Fantasma Vingador (The Phantom Brother) (also labeled no. 73), 26 pp.
      no. 16 A Memria Perdida (The Man with the Missing Memory) (also labeled no. 130), 24 pp.
      no. 17 Assassinato Nas Trevas (The Jekyll-Hyde Murders) (also labeled no. 116), 24 pp.
      no. 18 Fraternidade Maldita (Death is Just Around the Corner) (also labeled no. 117), 27 pp.
      no. 19 O Assassinato do Juiz (The Invisible Alibi) (also labeled no. 128), 25 pp.
      no. 20 O Diablico Plano de Lucifer (Lucifer has a Plan) (also labeled no. 121), 27 pp.
      no. 21 A Mascara da Morte (The Face of Death) (also labeled no. 163), 21 pp.
      no. 23 O Cadver Roubado (The Disappearing Corpse) (also labeled no. 124), 27 pp.
      no. 25 Cilada Contra o Sombra (The Brief Fame of John Copper) (also labeled no. 125), 24 pp.
      no. 26 A Caveira Luminosa (The Case of the Flaming Skull) (also labeled no. 112), 27 pp.
      no. 27 A Destruio de Nova York (The Destroyer) (also labeled no. 131), 24 pp.
      no. 28 Tragdia no Circo (The Sword of Dengri-la) (also labeled no. 114), 27 pp.
      no. 29 O Criminoso Invisivel (The Little Man Who Wasn't There) (also labeled no. 120), 24 pp.
    - 1945-46 season, 6 folders (Box 402)
      no. 1 O Ladro-Fantasma (The Shadow in Danger) (also labeled no. 147), 26 pp.
      no. 2 A Mensagem do Morto (The Thoughts of Death) (also labeled no. 149), 24 pp.
      no. 3 O Crime da Casa-Fantasma (Death in the Darkness) (also labeled no. 143), 23 pp.
      no. 4 Morte Nas Trevas (The Heartbeats of Death) (also labeled no. 158), 25 pp.
      no. 5 A Vingana do Cgo (Blind Man's Folly) (also labeled no. 141), 25 pp.
      no. 7 A Maldio do Pantano (Bayou) (also labeled no. 156), 23 pp.
      no. 8 Crime Por Amor (I Must Never Sleep Again) (also labeled no. 146), 25 pp.
      no. 9 O Misterio do bar dos Artistas (Spotlight on the Duchess) (also labeled no. 164), 25 pp.
      no. 10 A Morte Tece a Rede (Spider-Boy) (also labeled no. 138), 24 pp.
      no. 11 O Misterio da Torre do Farol (Death Rises out of the Sea) (also labeled no. 162), 21 pp.
      no. 12 Os Quatro Gigantes de Amsterdam (The Four Giants of Amsterdam) (also labeled no. 155), 26 pp.
      no. 13 O Brinde da Morte (Murder by Candlelight) (also labeled no. 150), 26 pp.
      no. 14 Armadilha Para o Crime (Relax and Murder) (also labeled no. 160), 21 pp.
      no. 15 Fantasmas Debaixo do Mar (The Ship of the Living Dead) (also labeled no. 154), 24 pp.
      no. 16 Crime na Vespera de Natal (Three Crimes on Christmas Eve) (also labeled no. 159), 24 pp.
      no. 17 O Que Voltou do Tumlo (Back from the Grave) (also labeled no. 145), 25 pp.
      no. 20 A Maldio da Selva (The Curse of the Cat) (also labeled no. 144), 24 pp.
      no. 21 O Salto da Morte (Dream of Death) (also labeled no. 148), 26 pp.
      no. 22 Entre Sedas Anda o Crime (Murder with Music) (also labeled no. 161), 20 pp.
      no. 23 A Cabea Viva (The Living Head) (also labeled no. 168), 20 pp.
      no. 24 A Morte por Encomenda (Murder for Money) (also labeled no. 142), 26 pp.
      no. 25 O Ritual Sinistro (The Hiss of Death) (also labeled no. 151), 24 pp.
      no. 26 O Drama no Pavilho (The Island of Ancient Death) (also labeled no. 139), 26 pp.
      no. 27 O Fantasma Sem Rosto (The Ghost without a Face) (also labeled no. 140), 22 pp.
    - 1945-46 season (cont.), 3 folders (Box 403)
      no. 28 Chantagem na Alta Roda (Etched with Acid) (also labeled no. 157), 25 pp.
      no. 29 O Misterio do Zombie (The Walking Corpse) (also labeled no. 153), 23 pp.
      no. 30 Os Tres Suicidios (Mind over Murder) (also labeled no. 152), 24 pp.
      no. 31 O Fantasma da Madrugada (The Ghost Wore a Silver Slipper) (also labeled no. 179), 21 pp.
      no. 32 Os Mortos Tambem Morrem (The Unburied Dead) (also labeled no. 175), 22 pp.
      no. 33 A Fera Humana (Gorilla Man) (also labeled no. 182), 25 pp.
      no. 34 A Sentena do Destino (The Dreams of Death) (also labeled no. 180), 24 pp.
      no. 35 O Feiticeiro da Ilha do Inferno (The White Witchman of Lawaiki) (also labeled no. 205), 23 pp.
      no. 36 A Familia Maldita (The Bride Wore Black) (also labeled no. 183), 27 pp.
      no. 37 Armadilha de Parafina (The Touch of Death) (also labeled no. 186), 25 pp.
      no. 38 A Quadrilha do Drago Negro (They Kill with a Silver Hatchet) (also labeled no. 176), 22 pp.
    - 1946-47 season, 4 folders (Box 403)
      no. 1 A Vampiro da Meia Noite (Vampires Prowl by Night) (also labeled no. 192), 21 pp.
      no. 2 A Volta do Passado (The Killer on High Cliff Road) (also labeled no. 172), 22 pp.
      no. 3 Resposta do Alem-Tumulo (Die, Love, Die) (also labeled no. 173), 22 pp.
      no. 5 O Vale do Terror (The Valley of Living Terror) (also labeled no. 198), 23 pp.
      no. 7 Sangue Por Dinheiro (Blood Money) (also labeled no. 170), 20 pp.
      no. 8 O Criador de Zombies (Cave of the Zombies) (also labeled no. 177), 19 pp.
      no. 9 Mortos Falsificados (Murder for Blackmail) (also labeled no. 195), 26 pp.
      no. 10 O Esfola Cadaver (The Corpse without a Skin) (also labeled no. 174), 24 pp.
      no. 11 O Fantasma do Campanrio (The Phantom of the Haunted Steeple) (also labeled no. 188), 21 pp.
      no. 13 Cemiterio de Vivos (Makeup for Murder) (also labeled no. 171), 21 pp.
      no. 14 Gargalhada da Morte (The Devil Takes a Wife) (also labeled no. 203), 21 pp.
      no. 15 Tragedia nos Bastidores (Murder on the Main Stem) (also labeled no. 201), 25 pp.
      no. 16 Sob a Beleza Sinistra do Luar... (The Fine Art of Murder) (also labeled no. 178), 21 pp.
      no. 17 Sombra de Suspeita (Shadow of Suspicion) (also labeled no. 211), 23 pp.
      no. 18 Sangue Sobre Neve (The Werewolf of Hamilton Mansion) (also labeled no. 213), 26 pp.
      no. 19 O Misterio da Coleira (The Cat and the Killer) (also labeled no. 216), 36 pp.
      no. 21 Tragedia no Hospcio (Death by Imagination) (also labeled no. 214), 24 pp.
      no. 22 O Perfume da Morte (The Scent of Death) (also labeled no. 212), 22 pp.
    - 1948-49 season, 2 folders (Box 403)
      no. 2 Ao Abrir to Tmulo (When the Grave is Open) (also labeled no. 254), 22 pp.
      no. 3 A Mascara nas Trevas (The Face) (also labeled no. 248), 23 pp.
      no. 4 Chantagem Contra Mulheres (Death Takes the Wheel) (also labeled no. 245), 21 pp.
      no. 5 Vingana de Sangue (The Curse of the Gypsies) (also labeled no. 250), 25 pp.
      no. 6 O Rubi de Kaarvahl (The Ruby of Karvahl) (also labeled no. 243), 21 pp.
      no. 7 Caada Humana (Death Hunt) (also labeled no. 244), 22 pp.
      no. 11 Assassino Silencioso (The Comic Strip Killer) (also labeled no. 242), 21 pp.
      no. 12 O Assassinato do Medium (Murder and the Medium) (also labeled no. 249), 25 pp.
      no. 13 A Quadrilha do Mar (Death Has Sharp Claws) (also labeled no. 256), 22 pp.
    - 1948-49 season (cont.), 3 folders (Box 404)
      no. 24 A Morte Ronda o Box (Death Takes the Long Count) (also labeled no. 241), 21 pp.
      no. 25 A Bruxa do Quarto Minguante (The Witch of the Crescent Moon) (also labeled no. 237), 22 pp.
      no. 26 A Morte Atia o Fogo (Death Fans the Flame) (also labeled no. 251), 23 pp.
      no. 27 O Misterio do Navio (Mystery Ship) (also labeled no. 238), 24 pp.
      no. 28 Assassino Logrado (Murder by Appointment) (also labeled no. 239), 23 pp.
      no. 29 Morte a Hora Certa (Death by Clockwork) (also labeled no. 252), 23 pp.
      no. 30 Garotos Criminosos (Crime in a Minor Key) (also labeled no. 247), 23 pp.
      no. 31 Crime na `Boite' (The Great White Way to Death) (also labeled no. 255), 23 pp.
      no. 32 O Roubo Escondido (Death is the Keeper) (also labeled no. 253), 24 pp.
      no. 33 Expionagem no Expresso (Murder Express) (also labeled no. 240), 22 pp.
      no. 35 A Liga Dos Suicidas (Suicide League) (also labeled no. 246), 22 pp.
      no. 36 A Forra do Assassino (The Shadow's Revenge) (also labeled no. 257), 23 pp.
      no. 37 Salto Para a Morte (Death Rides High) (also labeled no. 258), 23 pp.
  - Sonny Tabor
    - Episodes 1-18, all but no. 1 have 2 copies; also includes a 1-page bio of actors; 2 folders (Box 396)
- Miscellaneous
  - Author files, miscellaneous (Box 405)
  - Author/title list, unidentified (Box 406)
  - Clippings, miscellaneous (Box 406)
  - Correspondence, St. George Rathborne, 1922-1923; undated; 2 folders (Box 406)
  - Editor's notes, miscellaneous, includes notes on Adrienne's Revenge by Margaret Blount (Box 406)
  - "Good News" serials stories, 2 lists (Box 406)
  - "In Memoriam: Frank A Munsey", undated (Box 406)
  - Lovell's Quarterly Bulletin, Jan 1889 (Box 406)
  - Marketing materials for The Shadow, undated (Oversize 8)
  - Marketing materials for Tip Top Weekly, undated (Oversize 8)
  - Seaside Library, Pocket Edition, undated (Box 406)
  - Tear sheets, The Shadow comic, undated (Oversize 9)